<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<Document xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<Row>
		<symbol>AMTD</symbol>
		<company>TD Ameritrade Holding Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>26.2</open>
		<high>26.23</high>
		<low>25.54</low>
		<close>25.6</close>
		<volume>3200800</volume>
		<address>4211 South 102nd Street</address>
		<city>Omaha</city>
		<state>NE</state>
		<zip>68127</zip>
		<phone>402-331-7856</phone>
		<profile>TD Ameritrade Holding Corporation, through its subsidiaries, provides securities brokerage services and technology-based financial services to retail investors, traders, and independent registered investment advisors (RIAs) in the United States. The companys offerings include TD Ameritrade for self-directed retail investors; TD Ameritrade Institutional, which provides brokerage and custody services to independent RIAs and their clients; thinkorswim that offers a suite of trading platforms serving self-directed and institutional traders, and money managers; and Investools, which provides investor education products and services for stock, option, foreign exchange, futures, mutual fund, and fixed-income investors. Its offerings also include Amerivest, an online advisory service that develops portfolios of exchange-traded funds to enable long-term investors pursue their financial goals; and TD Ameritrade Corporate Services, which provides self-directed brokerage services to employees and executives of corporations. In addition, the company offers various products and services, such as common and preferred stocks; exchange-traded funds; a range of option trades, including complex, multi-leg option strategies; futures trades in various commodities, stock indices, and currencies; and foreign exchange products. Further, it provides mutual funds; treasury, corporate, government agency, and municipal bonds; mortgage-backed securities and certificates of deposit; new issue securities; margin lending; and cash management services. Additionally, the company offers trustee, custodial, and other trust-related services to retirement plans; and cash sweep and deposit account products through third-party relationships. It provides its products and services through the Internet, network of retail branches, mobile trading applications, and interactive voice response and registered representatives via telephone. The company was founded in 1971 and is headquartered in Omaha, Nebraska.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>BA</symbol>
		<company>Boeing Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>24.98</open>
		<high>24.98</high>
		<low>24.91</low>
		<close>24.93</close>
		<volume>49000</volume>
		<address>100 North Riverside Plaza</address>
		<city>Chicago</city>
		<state>IL</state>
		<zip>60606-1596</zip>
		<phone>312-544-2000</phone>
		<profile>The Boeing Company, together with its subsidiaries, engages in the design, development, manufacture, sale, and support of commercial jetliners, military aircraft, satellites, missile defense, human space flight, and launch systems and services worldwide. The company operates through five segments: Commercial Airplanes, Boeing Military Aircraft (BMA), Network and Space Systems (N&amp;SS), Global Services and Support (GS&amp;S), and Boeing Capital Corporation (BCC). The Commercial Airplanes segment develops, produces, and markets commercial jet aircraft for various passenger and cargo requirements, as well as provides related support services to the commercial airline industry. It also offers aviation services support, aircraft modifications, spares, training, maintenance documents, and technical advice to commercial and government customers. The BMA segment engages in the research, development, production, and modification of manned and unmanned military weapons systems for the global strike, mobility and surveillance, and engagement markets, as well as provides related services. The N&amp;SS segment is involved in the research, development, production, and modification of products and services to assist its customers in transforming their operations through its network integration, information and cyber applications, command, control, communications, computers, intelligence, surveillance, and reconnaissance space exploration and satellites. The GS&amp;S segment offers operations, maintenance, training, upgrades, and logistics support services for military platforms and operations. The BCC segment facilitates, arranges, structures, and provides financing solutions for its commercial airplanes customers and government customers. Its financing portfolio consists of equipment under operating leases, finance leases, notes and other receivables, assets held for sale or re-lease, and investments. The Boeing Company was founded in 1916 and is based in Chicago, Illinois.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>BAC</symbol>
		<company>Bank Of America Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>20.72</open>
		<high>20.72</high>
		<low>20.58</low>
		<close>20.63</close>
		<volume>12200</volume>
		<address>100 North Tryon Street</address>
		<city>Charlotte</city>
		<state>NC</state>
		<zip>28255</zip>
		<phone>704-386-5681</phone>
		<profile>Bank of America Corporation, through its subsidiaries, provides various banking and financial products and services to individual consumers, small-and middle-market businesses, institutional investors, corporations, and governments in the United States and internationally. The companys Deposits segment provides traditional savings accounts, money market savings accounts, CDs and IRAs, and noninterest-and interest-bearing checking accounts, as well as investment accounts and products. Its Card Services segment issues credit and debit cards in the United States providing a range of lending products, including co-branded and affinity products. The companys Consumer Real Estate Services segment offers a line of consumer real estate products and services comprising fixed and adjustable-rate first-lien mortgage loans for home purchase and refinancing needs, home equity lines of credit, and home equity loans. Its Global Commercial Banking segment provides a range of lending-related products and services, integrated working capital management, and treasury solutions to business banking and middle-market companies, commercial real estate firms, and governments. The companys Global Banking &amp; Markets segment offers advisory services, financing, securities clearing, settlement, and custody services to institutional investor clients; debt and equity underwriting and distribution; merger-related and other advisory services; and risk management products. Its Global Wealth &amp; Investment Management segment provides brokerage, banking, and retirement products; wealth structuring, investment management, trust and banking needs, and asset management services; and institutional and personal retirement solutions. As of May 12, 2012, the company served customers through a network of 5,700 banking centers, 17,750 ATMs, call centers, and online and mobile banking platforms. Bank of America Corporation was founded in 1874 and is based in Charlotte, North Carolina.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>KO</symbol>
		<company>Coca-Cola Enterprises</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>41.5</open>
		<high>41.5</high>
		<low>40.16</low>
		<close>40.16</close>
		<volume>700</volume>
		<address>One Coca-Cola Plaza</address>
		<city>Atlanta</city>
		<state>GA</state>
		<zip>30313</zip>
		<phone>404-676-2121</phone>
		<profile>The Coca-Cola Company, a beverage company, engages in the manufacture, marketing, and sale of nonalcoholic beverages worldwide. The company primarily offers sparkling beverages and still beverages. Its sparkling beverages include nonalcoholic ready-to-drink beverages with carbonation, such as carbonated energy drinks, and carbonated waters and flavored waters. The companys still beverages comprise nonalcoholic beverages without carbonation, such as noncarbonated waters, flavored waters and enhanced waters, noncarbonated energy drinks, juices and juice drinks, ready-to-drink teas and coffees, and sports drinks. It also provides flavoring ingredients, sweeteners, powders for purified water products, beverage ingredients, and fountain syrups. The Coca-Cola Company sells its products primarily under the Diet Coke, Fanta, Sprite, Coca-Cola Zero, vitaminwater, Powerade, Minute Maid, Simply, Georgia, and Del Valle brand names. The company offers its beverage products through company-owned or controlled bottling and distribution operators, as well as through independently owned bottling partners, distributors, wholesalers, and retailers. The Coca-Cola Company was founded in 1886 and is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>FDX</symbol>
		<company>Fedex Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>21.1</open>
		<high>21.12</high>
		<low>20.97</low>
		<close>21.11</close>
		<volume>31800</volume>
		<address>942 South Shady Grove Road</address>
		<city>Memphis</city>
		<state>TN</state>
		<zip>38120</zip>
		<phone>901-818-7500</phone>
		<profile>FedEx Corporation provides transportation, e-commerce, and business services in the United States and internationally. It operates in four segments: FedEx Express, FedEx Ground, FedEx Freight, and FedEx Services. The FedEx Express segment offers various shipping services for the delivery of packages and freight. This segment also provides international trade services specializing in customs brokerage, and ocean and air freight forwarding services; customs clearance services, as well as global trade data, an information tool that allows customers to track and manage imports; and international trade advisory services, including assistance with the customs-trade partnership against terrorism program, as well as publishes customs duty and tax information in various customs areas. In addition, it offers supply chain solutions, including critical inventory logistics, transportation management, and temperature-controlled transportation services. The FedEx Ground segment provides business and residential ground package delivery services; and engages in the consolidation and delivery of high volumes of low-weight and less time-sensitive business-to-consumer packages. It primarily serves customers in the small-package market in North America. The FedEx Freight segment offers less-than-truckload freight services, as well as freight-shipping services. As of May 31, 2012, this segment operated approximately 58,000 vehicles and trailers from a network of 366 service centers. The FedEx Services segment provides sales, marketing, information technology, communications, customer service support, and other back-office support services; and access to copying and digital printing through retail and Web-based platforms, signs and graphics, professional finishing, computer rentals, and a range of ground shipping and time-definite express shipping services. The company was founded in 1971 and is headquartered in Memphis, Tennessee.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>GD</symbol>
		<company>General Dynamics Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>14.47</open>
		<high>14.52</high>
		<low>14.47</low>
		<close>14.51</close>
		<volume>20700</volume>
		<address>2941 Fairview Park Drive, Suite 100</address>
		<city>Falls Church</city>
		<state>VA</state>
		<zip>22042-4153</zip>
		<phone>703-876-3000</phone>
		<profile>General Dynamics Corporation, an aerospace and defense company, provides business aviation; combat vehicles, weapons systems, and munitions; military and commercial shipbuilding; and communications and information technology products and services worldwide. Its Aerospace group designs, manufactures, and outfits various large and mid-cabin business-jet aircraft; provides maintenance, repair work, fixed-based operations, and aircraft management services; and performs aircraft completions for aircraft. The companys Combat Systems group offers tracked and wheeled military vehicles, weapons systems, and munitions. Its product lines include wheeled combat and tactical vehicles; battle tanks and infantry vehicles; munitions and propellant; rockets and gun systems; and axle and drivetrain components and aftermarket parts. This group also manufactures and supplies engineered axles, suspensions, and brakes for heavy-load vehicles for military and commercial customers. The companys Marine System group designs, builds, and supports submarines and surface ships for the U.S. Navy; and Jones Act ships for commercial customers. This group offers nuclear-powered submarines, surface combatants, and auxiliary and commercial ships; and provides design and engineering support services, as well as ship and submarine overhaul, repair, and lifecycle support services. Its Information Systems and Technology group provides technologies, products, and services that support a range of government and commercial communication, and information-sharing needs, including communications systems, command-and-control systems, and operational hardware; information technology services; and intelligence, surveillance, reconnaissance, and tactical communication systems to the U.S. defense, intelligence and homeland security communities, the U.S. allies, and commercial and international customers. General Dynamics Corporation was founded in 1899 and is based in Falls Church, Virginia.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>GE</symbol>
		<company>General Electric Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>18.62</open>
		<high>18.75</high>
		<low>18.5</low>
		<close>18.63</close>
		<volume>2999000</volume>
		<address>3135 Easton Turnpike</address>
		<city>Fairfield</city>
		<state>CT</state>
		<zip>06828-0001</zip>
		<phone>203-373-2211</phone>
		<profile>General Electric Company operates as a technology and financial services company worldwide. The companys Energy Infrastructure segment offers wind turbines; gas and steam turbines and generators; integrated gasification combined cycle systems; aircraft engine derivatives; nuclear reactors, fuel, and support services; oil and gas extraction and mining motors and control systems; aftermarket services; water treatment solutions; power conversion infrastructure technology and services; and integrated electrical equipment and systems. This segment also provides surface and subsea drilling and production systems, equipment for floating production platforms, compressors, turbines, turboexpanders, high pressure reactors, and industrial power generation and auxiliary equipment, as well as pipeline integrity, measurement, inspection, monitoring, and radiation measurement solutions to the oil and gas industry. Its Aviation segment offers jet engines, turboprop and turbo shaft engines, related replacement parts, and aerospace systems and equipment for use in military and commercial aircraft; and maintenance, component repair, and overhaul services. The companys Healthcare segment provides medical imaging and information technologies, medical diagnostics, patient monitoring systems, disease research, drug discovery, biopharmaceutical manufacturing technologies, and remote diagnostic and repair services. Its Transportation segment provides drive technology solutions to various industries, including railroad, transit, mining, oil and gas, power generation, and marine. The companys Home and Business Solutions segment provides home appliances; lighting products; and plant automation, hardware, software, and embedded computing systems. Its GE Capital segment offers commercial loans and leases, fleet management, financial programs, home loans, credit cards, personal loans, and other financial services. The company was founded in 1892 and is headquartered in Fairfield, Connecticut.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>GM</symbol>
		<company>General Motors Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>10.11</open>
		<high>10.3</high>
		<low>10.06</low>
		<close>10.28</close>
		<volume>626000</volume>
		<address>300 Renaissance Center</address>
		<city>Detroit</city>
		<state>MI</state>
		<zip>48265-3000</zip>
		<phone>313-556-5000</phone>
		<profile>General Motors Company (GM) designs, manufactures, and markets cars, crossovers, trucks, and automobile parts worldwide. The company markets its vehicles primarily under the Buick, Cadillac, Chevrolet, GMC, Opel, Daewoo, Holden, and Vauxhall brand names, as well as under the Alpheon, Jiefang, Baojun, and Wuling brand names. It also sells cars and trucks to dealers for consumer retail sales, as well as to fleet customers, including daily rental car companies, commercial fleet customers, leasing companies, and governments. In addition, the company offers connected safety, security and mobility solutions, and information technology services. The company, through its subsidiary, General Motors Financial Company, Inc. provides automotive financing services and lease products through GM dealerships in connection with the sale of used and new automobiles that target customers with sub-prime and prime credit bureau scores. The company was founded in 1908 and is based in Detroit, Michigan.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>WFC</symbol>
		<company>Wells Fargo &amp; Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>27.55</open>
		<high>27.6</high>
		<low>27.26</low>
		<close>27.44</close>
		<volume>445000</volume>
		<address>420 Montgomery Street</address>
		<city>San Francisco</city>
		<state>CA</state>
		<zip>94194</zip>
		<phone>866-878-5865</phone>
		<profile>Wells Fargo &amp; Company, through its subsidiaries, provides retail, commercial, and corporate banking services primarily in the United States. The company operates in three segments: Community Banking; Wholesale Banking; and Wealth, Brokerage, and Retirement. The Community Banking segment offers deposits, including checking, market rate, and individual retirement accounts; savings and time deposits; and debit cards. Its loan products comprise lines of credit, auto floor plans, equity lines and loans, equipment and transportation loans, education loans, residential mortgage loans, health savings accounts, and credit cards. This segment also provides equipment leases, real estate financing, small business administration financing, venture capital financing, cash management, payroll services, retirement plans, loans secured by autos, and merchant payment processing services; purchases sales finance contracts from retail merchants; and a family of funds, and investment management services. The Wholesale Banking segment offers commercial and corporate banking products and services, including commercial loans and lines of credit, letters of credit, asset-based lending, equipment leasing, international trade facilities, trade financing, collection services, foreign exchange services, treasury and investment management, institutional fixed-income sales, commodity and equity risk management, insurance, corporate trust fiduciary and agency services, and investment banking services. This segment also provides banking products for commercial real estate market, and real estate and mortgage brokerage services. The Wealth, Brokerage, and Retirement segment offers financial advisory, brokerage, and institutional retirement and trust services. As of December 31, 2010, the company served its customers through approximately 9,000 banking stores in 39 States and the District of Columbia. Wells Fargo &amp; Company was founded in 1929 and is headquartered in San Francisco, California.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>KIM</symbol>
		<company>Kimco Realty Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>24.62</open>
		<high>24.64</high>
		<low>24.5</low>
		<close>24.54</close>
		<volume>155200</volume>
		<address>3333 New Hyde Park Road, Suite 100</address>
		<city>New Hyde Park</city>
		<state>NY</state>
		<zip>11042</zip>
		<phone>516-869-9000</phone>
		<profile>Kimco Realty Corporation is an independent real estate investment trust. The firm invests in the real estate markets across North America. It is primarily engaged in acquisitions, development, and management of neighborhood and community shopping centers. The firm also provides property management services relating to the management, leasing, operation, and maintenance of real estate properties. Kimco Realty Corporation was formed in 1966 and is based in New Hyde Park, New York with additional office all across North America.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>MCD</symbol>
		<company>Mcdonald's Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>26.44</open>
		<high>26.55</high>
		<low>26.42</low>
		<close>26.5</close>
		<volume>1800</volume>
		<address>One McDonald</address>
		<city>Oak Brook</city>
		<state>IL</state>
		<zip>60523</zip>
		<phone>630-623-3000</phone>
		<profile>McDonalds Corporation, together with its subsidiaries, franchises and operates McDonalds restaurants primarily in the United States, Europe, the Asia Pacific, the Middle East, and Africa. The companys restaurants offer hamburgers and cheeseburgers, Big Mac, Quarter Pounder with cheese, Filet-O-Fish, chicken sandwiches, chicken McNuggets, chicken selects, snack wraps, french fries, salads, shakes, desserts, sundaes, soft serve cones, pies, cookies, soft drinks, coffee, and other beverages, as well as full or limited breakfast menu. As of December 31, 2011, it operated 33,510 restaurants in 119 countries, including 27,075 franchised restaurants and 6,435 company operated restaurants. The company was founded in 1940 and is based in Oak Brook, Illinois.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>MMM</symbol>
		<company>3M Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>15.9</open>
		<high>15.98</high>
		<low>15.63</low>
		<close>15.72</close>
		<volume>3832500</volume>
		<address>3-M Center</address>
		<city>St Paul</city>
		<state>MN</state>
		<zip>55144-1000</zip>
		<phone>651-733-1110</phone>
		<profile>3M Company operates as a diversified technology company worldwide. The companys Industrial and Transportation segment offers tapes, coated and non-woven abrasives, adhesives, specialty materials, filtration products, energy control products, closure systems for personal hygiene products, acoustic systems products, and components and products used in the manufacture, repair, and maintenance of automotive, marine, aircraft, and specialty vehicles. Its Health Care segment provides medical and surgical supplies, skin health and infection prevention products, inhalation and transdermal drug delivery systems, dental and orthodontic products, health information systems, and food safety products. The companys Consumer and Office segment provides office supply, stationery, construction and home improvement, home care, protective material, certain consumer retail personal safety, and consumer health care products. Its Safety, Security and Protection Services segment offers personal protection products, cleaning and protection products for commercial establishments, safety and security products, roofing granules for asphalt shingles, corrosion protection products used in the oil and gas pipeline markets, and track and trace solutions. The companys Display and Graphics offers optical film solutions for LCD electronic displays; computer screen filters; reflective sheeting for transportation safety; commercial graphics sheeting and systems; architectural surface and lighting solutions; and mobile interactive solutions, including mobile display technology, visual systems products, and computer privacy filters. Its Electro and Communications segment provides packaging and interconnection devices; fluids used in the manufacture of computer chips, and for cooling electronics and lubricating computer hard disk drives; high-temperature and display tapes; and insulating materials, including tapes and resins. The company was founded in 1902 and is based in St. Paul, Minnesota.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>MS</symbol>
		<company>Morgan Stanley</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>6.48</open>
		<high>6.78</high>
		<low>6.48</low>
		<close>6.78</close>
		<volume>975900</volume>
		<address>1585 Broadway</address>
		<city>New York</city>
		<state>NY</state>
		<zip>10036</zip>
		<phone>212-761-4000</phone>
		<profile>Morgan Stanley, a financial holding company, provides various financial products and services to corporations, governments, financial institutions, and individuals worldwide. The companys Institutional Securities segment offers financial advisory services on mergers and acquisitions, divestitures, joint ventures, corporate restructurings, recapitalizations, spin-offs, exchange offers, leveraged buyouts, takeover defenses, and shareholder relations, as well as capital raising and corporate lending services. This segment also engages in investment activities; and sales, trading, financing, and market-making activities, including equity trading, interest rates, credit and currencies, and commodities, as well as financing services, such as prime brokerage, consolidated clearance, settlement, custody, financing, and portfolio reporting services. Its Global Wealth Management Group segment provides brokerage and investment advisory services covering various investments comprising equities, options, futures, foreign currencies, precious metals, fixed income securities, mutual funds, structured products, alternative investments, unit investment trusts, managed futures, separately managed accounts, and mutual fund asset allocation programs; education savings programs, financial and wealth planning services, and annuity and other insurance products; credit and other lending products; cash management services; retirement services; and trust and fiduciary services, as well as engages in fixed income principal trading. The companys Asset Management segment offers products and services in the areas of equity and fixed income; and alternative investments, such as hedge funds, funds of hedge funds, funds of private equity funds, and portable alpha strategies to institutional and intermediary channels; and high net worth clients. This segment also engages in real estate and merchant banking activities. Morgan Stanley was founded in 1935 and is headquartered in New York, New York.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>MTD</symbol>
		<company>Mettler-Toledo International</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>15.32</open>
		<high>15.32</high>
		<low>15.15</low>
		<close>15.23</close>
		<volume>67300</volume>
		<address>1900 Polaris Parkway</address>
		<city>Columbus</city>
		<state>OH</state>
		<zip>43240</zip>
		<phone>614-438-4511</phone>
		<profile>Mettler-Toledo International Inc. engages in the research, development, manufacture, and marketing of precision instruments and software primarily in Europe, North and South America, and Asia. The company offers weighing instruments for use in laboratory, industrial, packaging, logistics, and food retailing applications; analytical instruments for use in life science; reaction engineering and real-time analytic systems used in drug and chemical compound development; and process analytics instruments used for in-line measurement in production processes. Its laboratory instruments include laboratory balances, pipettes, titrators, thermal analysis systems, pH meters, density and refractometry instruments, moisture analyzers, laboratory software, automated chemistry solutions, and process analytic instruments. The companys industrial solutions include industrial weighing instruments, industrial terminals, automatic identification and data capture solutions, vehicle scale systems, industrial software, and product inspection systems. Its retail solutions include multiple weighing and food labeling solutions consisting of stand-alone scales, networked scales, and software for handling fresh goods, such as meats, vegetables, fruits, and cheeses. The companys principal customers include the life science industry covering pharmaceutical and biotechnology companies, and independent research organizations; food and beverage producers; food retailers; chemical, specialty chemical, and cosmetics companies; transportation and logistics, metals, and electronics industries; and the academic community. The company markets its products through its direct sales forces, as well as through indirect distribution channels. Mettler-Toledo International Inc. was founded in 1991 and is based in Columbus, Ohio.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>NYT</symbol>
		<company>New York Times Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>10.65</open>
		<high>10.65</high>
		<low>10.54</low>
		<close>10.55</close>
		<volume>85900</volume>
		<address>620 Eighth Avenue</address>
		<city>New York</city>
		<state>NY</state>
		<zip>10018</zip>
		<phone>212-556-1234</phone>
		<profile>The New York Times Company operates as a multimedia news and information company primarily in the United States. It operates in two segments, News Media Group and About Group. The News Media segment consists of the New York Times Media Group and the New England Media Group. The New York Times Media Group comprises the New York Times, a daily and Sunday newspaper; the International Herald Tribune, a daily newspaper; NYTimes.com; the New York Times Index, which produces and licenses the New York Times Index, a print publication; Digital Archive Distribution business that licenses electronic archive databases to resellers of that information in the business, professional, and library markets; and the New York Times News Services Division, which transmits articles, graphics, and photographs from The Times, the Globe, and other publications to newspapers, magazines, and Websites, as well as owns interest in Epsilen, LLC, an online education business. It also distributes content online, as well as on other digital platforms, including mobile and e-reader applications and social networking sites. The New England Media Group includes the Boston Globe, a daily and Sunday newspaper; BostonGlobe.com and Boston.com, which are news and information Websites; the Worcester Telegram &amp; Gazette, a daily newspaper; and Telegram.com. The About Group segment consists of the Websites of About.com, ConsumerSearch.com, and CalorieCount.com. About.com focuses on delivering content on everyday topics; ConsumerSearch.com analyzes expert and user-generated consumer product reviews; and CalorieCount.com offers weight management tools, nutritional information, and social support. The company also holds an interest in New England Sports Network, a regional cable sports network that televises the Red Sox and Boston Bruins hockey games. The New York Times Company was founded in 1896 and is headquartered in New York, New York.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>PG</symbol>
		<company>Procter &amp; Gamble Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>28.5</open>
		<high>28.65</high>
		<low>28.3</low>
		<close>28.65</close>
		<volume>203700</volume>
		<address>One Procter &amp; Gamble Plaza</address>
		<city>Cincinnati</city>
		<state>OH</state>
		<zip>45202</zip>
		<phone>513-983-1100</phone>
		<profile>The Procter &amp; Gamble Company, together with its subsidiaries, engages in the manufacture and sale of a range of branded consumer packaged goods. The company operates in five segments: Beauty, Grooming, Health Care, Fabric Care and Home Care, and Baby Care and Family Care. The Beauty segment provides antiperspirants, deodorants, cosmetics, hair care products, hair colors, personal cleansings, prestige products, professional salon products, and skin care products primarily under the Head &amp; Shoulders, Olay, Pantene, SK-II, and Wella brand names. The Grooming segment offers blades and razors, electronic hair removal devices, hair care appliances, and pre and post shave products primarily under the Braun, Fusion, Gillette, and Mach3 brand names. The Health Care segment provides feminine care, gastrointestinal, incontinence, rapid diagnostics, respiratory, toothbrush, toothpaste, oral care, and other personal health care products, as well as vitamins/minerals/supplements primarily under the Always, Crest, Oral-B, and Vicks brand names. The Fabric Care and Home Care segment offers bleach and laundry additives, air care products, batteries, dish care items, fabric enhancers, laundry detergents, pet care products, and surface care products primarily under the Ace, Ariel, Dawn, Downy, Duracell, Febreze, Gain, Iams, and Tide brand names. The Baby Care and Family Care segment provides baby wipes, diapers and pants, paper towels, tissues, and toilet papers primarily under the Bounty, Charmin, and Pampers brand names. The company markets its products through mass merchandisers, grocery stores, membership club stores, drug stores, high-frequency stores, department stores, perfumeries, pharmacies, salons, and e-commerce in approximately 180 countries worldwide. The Procter &amp; Gamble Company was founded in 1837 and is based in Cincinnati, Ohio.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>SCHW</symbol>
		<company>The Charles Schwab Corporation</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>10.5</open>
		<high>10.52</high>
		<low>10.48</low>
		<close>10.52</close>
		<volume>35900</volume>
		<address>211 Main Street</address>
		<city>San Francisco</city>
		<state>CA</state>
		<zip>94105</zip>
		<phone>415-667-7000</phone>
		<profile>The Charles Schwab Corporation, through its subsidiaries, provides securities brokerage, banking, and related financial services to individuals and institutional clients. It offers various brokerage products and services comprising brokerage accounts with check-writing features, debit card, and billpay; individual retirement accounts; retirement plans for small to large businesses; college savings accounts; designated brokerage accounts; equity incentive plan accounts; and margin loans, as well as access to fixed income securities, equity and debt offerings, options, and futures. The company also provides various banking products and services, including checking accounts linked to brokerage accounts, savings accounts, certificates of deposit, demand deposit accounts, first mortgages, home equity lines of credit, and personal loans collateralized by securities. In addition, it offers trust custody services, personal trust reporting services, and administrative trustee services; advisory services comprising separately managed accounts, customized personal advice for tailored portfolios, and planning and portfolio management; and third-party mutual funds, such as no-load mutual funds, proprietary mutual funds, and other third-party mutual funds, as well as mutual fund trading and clearing services to broker dealers. Further, the company offers third-party and proprietary exchange-traded funds; research, analytic tools, performance reports, market analysis, and educational materials; custodial, trading, technology, practice management, trust asset, and other support services to independent investment advisors; and retirement plan recordkeeping and related services, retirement plan trust and custody services, specialty brokerage services, and mutual fund clearing services. It operates primarily in the United States, the United Kingdom, and Hong Kong. The company was founded in 1971 and is headquartered in San Francisco, California.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>TAP</symbol>
		<company>Molson Coors Brewing Company</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>37.25</open>
		<high>37.36</high>
		<low>36.78</low>
		<close>36.94</close>
		<volume>267500</volume>
		<address>1225 17th Street, Suite 3200</address>
		<city>Denver</city>
		<state>CO</state>
		<zip>80202</zip>
		<phone>303-927-2337</phone>
		<profile>Molson Coors Brewing Company manufactures and sells beer and other beverage products. The company sells its products in Canada, under the Coors Light, Molson Canadian, Molson Export, Molson Canadian 67, Molson Dry, Molson M, Rickard's Red, Rickard's Blonde and other Rickard's brands, Carling, Carling Black Label, Pilsner, Keystone, Creemore Springs, Granville Island brands, Caffrey's, and Cobra; and various regional brands. The company also brews or distributes products under license under the Heineken, Amstel Light, Murphy's, Asahi, Asahi Select, Miller Lite, Miller Genuine Draft, Miller Chill, Milwaukee's Best, Milwaukee's Best Dry, and Foster's brands. In addition, it distributes the Corona, Coronita, Negra Modelo, and Pacifico brands, through a joint venture agreement with Grupo Modelo S.A.B. de C.V., as well as Singha brand. Further, the company sells various brands in the United States comprising Coors Light, Miller Lite, Coors Banquet, Miller Genuine Draft, Miller 64, Miller Chill, Sparks, Miller High Life, Keystone, Icehouse, Mickey's, Milwaukee's Best, Hamm's, Old English 800, Blue Moon, Henry Weinhard's, George Killian's Irish Red, Leinenkugel's, Peroni Nastro Azzurro, Pilsner Urquell, Grolsch, Coors Non-Alcoholic, and Sharp's. Additionally, it sells various brands in the United Kingdom that include Carling, C2, Carling Chrome, Coors Light, Worthington's, White Shield, Red Shield, Caffrey's, Sharp's Doom Bar, Animée, and Blue Moon; and various regional ale brands, and factored brands, such as wines. The company also sells brands through a joint venture with Royal Grolsch N.V. and a joint venture called Cobra Beer Partnership Ltd. In addition, it sells Zima, Si'hai, Coors Gold, and Coors Extra brands. The company was formerly known as Adolph Coors Company and changed its name to Molson Coors Brewing Company in February 2005 as a result of its merger with Molson Inc. Molson Coors Brewing Company was founded in 1873 and is headquartered in Denver, Colorado.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>UPS</symbol>
		<company>United Parcel Service</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>12.98</open>
		<high>13.11</high>
		<low>12.98</low>
		<close>13.05</close>
		<volume>101700</volume>
		<address>55 Glenlake Parkway NE</address>
		<city>Atlanta</city>
		<state>GA</state>
		<zip>30328</zip>
		<phone>404-828-6000</phone>
		<profile>United Parcel Service, Inc., a package delivery company, provides transportation, logistics, and financial services in the United States and internationally. It operates in three segments: U.S. Domestic Package, International Package, and Supply Chain &amp; Freight. The U.S. Domestic Package segment is involved in the time-definite delivery of letters, documents, and packages in the United States. The International Package segment provides delivery services to approximately 220 countries and territories, including shipments outside the United States, as well as shipments with either origin or destination outside the United States. The Supply Chain &amp; Freight segment offers forwarding and logistics services, such as supply chain design and management, freight distribution, customs brokerage, mail, and consulting services in approximately 195 countries and territories; and less-than-truckload and truckload services to customers in North America. The company also offers various technology solutions for shipping, visibility, and billing, as well as provides export and import financing; payment solutions; and risk mitigation offerings. It operates a fleet of approximately 101,000 package cars, vans, tractors, and motorcycles; an air fleet of 523 aircraft; and 35,000 containers used to transport cargo in its aircraft. United Parcel Service, Inc. was founded in 1907 and is headquartered in Atlanta, Georgia.</profile>
	</Row>
	<Row>
		<symbol>VZ</symbol>
		<company>Verizon Communications Inc.</company>
		<date>13-Aug-12</date>
		<open>3.76</open>
		<high>3.76</high>
		<low>3.65</low>
		<close>3.76</close>
		<volume>1600</volume>
		<address>140 West Street</address>
		<city>New York</city>
		<state>NY</state>
		<zip>10007</zip>
		<phone>212-395-1000</phone>
		<profile>Verizon Communications Inc. provides communications, information, and entertainment products and services to consumers, businesses, and governmental agencies worldwide. Its Verizon Wireless segment offers data services and applications comprising Internet access through smart phones and basic phones; mobile broadband services; messaging services, which enable its customers to send and receive text, picture, and video messages; customer-focused and business-focused offerings; location-based services; and global data services, as well as access to data applications and services of third parties. This segment also provides voice services; other connection-related services, such as data access and value added services to support telemetry-type applications; and M2M services that support devices used in healthcare, manufacturing, utilities, distribution, and consumer products markets, as well as sells smart phones and basic phones, tablets, and other Internet access devices. The companys Wireline segment offers video services over its fiber-optic network; data Services comprising high-speed Internet and FiOS broadband data products, as well as local exchange capacity, managed, mobility, and security services; voice services, such as local exchange, regional, long distance, wire maintenance, and voice messaging services, as well as VoIP, and landline and wireless services; and local dial tone and broadband services to local exchange carriers. This segment also provides networking products and solutions, such as private Internet protocol services, and Ethernet access and ring services; and infrastructure and cloud services. As of August 10, 2012, it served 94.2 million retail customers, including 88.8 million retail postpaid customers. The company was formerly known as Bell Atlantic Corporation and changed its name to Verizon Communications Inc. in June 2000. Verizon Communications Inc. was founded in 1983 and is based in New York, New York.</profile>
	</Row>
</Document>